on2.com 2005-04-03

# On2 Technologies

At On2.com, we intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information, including registration data. We will let each user know how we will use the personal information derived from each user's access to and use of On2.com and TrueMotion.com (the “On2 Websites”) and/or the Services.

We disclose how we will be using our customers' information through documents like this one, or by answering individual questions customers may ask.

We NEVER sell our customers' registration information or provide it to others.

The On2 Websites contain links to other websites, whether owned or controlled by On2 Technologies, affiliates or unrelated third parties. On2 Technologies is not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of any linked website.

Currently, On2 Technologies uses personal information as a basis for notifications to users, product release notices, "opt-in" emails, and making available other products and services to you and other customers or potential customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to the On2 Websites, new products or services and special offers we think you may find valuable. However, in cases where users voluntarily and publicly disclose personal information that may contain registration data, or otherwise post personal information in conjunction with content subject to an open source license, such personal information necessarily will be disclosed subject to the terms of the applicable license.

Subject to the foregoing, On2 Technologies may conduct surveys of other studies of its customer base and usage for marketing and planning purposes. With respect to information collected from such surveys or studies, and in the event that responses are to be publicly disclosed, users will be notified at the time they take the survey and On2 Technologies will disclose only aggregate information regarding its users and not personal information identifying any specific individual. Notwithstanding the foregoing, in cases where surveys allow users to submit written comments, and where On2 Technologies advises users of the possibility of such disclosure at the time they take the survey, On2 Technologies reserves the right to disclose text information provided by any user through such a survey, provided that no personal information identifying that user is disclosed.

**Security**

To secure site integrity, On2 Technologies employs measures including but not limited to security audits, use of encryption tools and software, and other reasonable security measures and procedures. Internal access to users' private and nonpublic personal information is restricted to site administrators and individuals on a need-to-know basis.

**Enforcement**

In the event that On2 Technologies becomes aware that site security is compromised or user nonpublic information has been disclosed to unrelated third parties as a result of external activity, including but not limited to external security attacks, On2 Technologies shall take reasonable measures which it deems appropriate, including but not limited to internal investigation and reporting, and notification to and cooperation with law enforcement authorities.

If On2 Technologies becomes aware that a user's personal information provided to us on one of the On2 websites has been disclosed in a manner not permitted by this Privacy Policy, On2 Technologies shall make reasonable efforts to notify the affected user, as soon as reasonably possible and as permitted by law, of what information has been disclosed, to the extent that On2 Technologies knows this information.

© 2001-2005 On2 Technologies, Inc. All rights reserved.
